export default data = [
  {
      question: "Chinese parents are usually very _____ of their children. They want to make sure their children are safe and well taken care of all the time.",
      options: ["patient","peculiar","protective","persuasive"],
      correct_option: "protective"
  },
  {
      question: "On receiving my letter of complaint, the hotel manager sent me a written ______.",
      options: ["consent","scandal","lecture","apology"],
      correct_option: "apology"
  },
  {
      question: "Jordan’s performance _______ his teammates and they finally beat their opponents to win the championship.",
      options: ["signaled","promoted","opposed","inspired"],
      correct_option: "inspired"
  },
  {
      question: "Mr. Lin’s comments were very difficult to follow because they were _____ related to the topic under discussion.",
      options: ["loosely","specifically","anxiously","typically"],
      correct_option: "loosely"
  },
  {
      question: "Jack came from a poor family, so his parents had to _____ many things to pay for his education.",
      options: ["inherit","qualify","sacrifice","purchase"],
      correct_option: "sacrifice"
  },
  {
      question: "The _____ of SARS has caused great inconvenience to many families in Taiwan.",
      options: ["destiny","contempt","outbreak","isolation"],
      correct_option: "outbreak"
  },
  {
      question: "Victor’s classmates are very ____ of him because he has just received a new cell phone for his birthday.",
      options: ["arrogant","envious","beloved","logical"],
      correct_option: "envious"
  },
  {
      question: "Some people still believe, quite _____, that one can get AIDS by shaking hands with homosexuals.",
      options: ["hardly","consequently","mistakenly","generously"],
      correct_option: "mistakenly"
  },
  {
      question: "There are altogether 154 foreign students in this university, ____ a total of thirteen different countries. ",
      options: ["constructing","representing","exploiting","participating"],
      correct_option: "representing"
  },
  {
      question: "During a _____, many people become unemployed and very few new jobs are available.",
      options: ["recession","prediction","government","disappointment"],
      correct_option: "recession"
  },
  {
      question: "Mr. and Mrs. Wang were worried about their baby girl because she _____ with the flu again. ",
      options: ["put up","went forward","looked after","came down"],
      correct_option: "came down"
  },
  {
      question: "Spider Man star Tobey Maguire may be forced to _____ the sequel because of his back injury.",
      options: ["back out of","set foot in","make use of","keep up with"],
      correct_option: "back out of"
  },
  {
      question: "Because many students were kept _____ about the lecture, the attendance was much smaller than expected.",
      options: ["out of order","on thin ice","without a doubt","in the dark"],
      correct_option: "in the dark"
  },
  {
      question: "All his hard work in the past three years has _____ now that the student has graduated with top honors.",
      options: ["given in","paid off","fallen apart","come about"],
      correct_option: "paid off"
  },
  {
      question: "It’s quite safe here in the city. You don’t need to _____ when taking a walk—even at night.",
      options: ["watch your back","slip your mind","break your neck","catch your breath"],
      correct_option: "watch your back"
  },
]